[{"answer": "It is incredible for the family.", "docId": "130605pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "How important is it to the family that you've managed to have this legal success?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "Yes, it was a very puzzling argument, which was they didn't have enough data.", "docId": "130605pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "I mean, what is the argument that stops somebody like Sarah from having this kind of transplant from an adult donor?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "We don't understand it.", "docId": "130605pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "What is your view as a family of the secretary's position?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "We're very hopeful.", "docId": "130605pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "How hopeful are you, from all the experts have told you, that you may get one?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "I would.", "docId": "130605pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "If that was the circumstance, would you be in favor of that?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "I'm doing well.", "docId": "130605pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "My first question, how are you?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "I had just been released from the hospital.", "docId": "130605pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "Where were you when that happened?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "So we got to ride out and -- just not again.", "docId": "130605pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "What were you thinking?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130605pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "Now, Ashlynn, did you realize how serious the tornado was at the time?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "After -- I was -- I was kind of the one who noticed that it was through her leg.", "docId": "130605pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "And did you realize, Ashlynn, that your mom had been a hero in protecting all of you?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "Well, I didn't see it in her leg.", "docId": "130605pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "And, Miranda, Miranda, what did you think when you saw your poor mother had this terrible spike in her leg?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130605pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "Pretty scary to look at, huh?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "I think, as Oklahomans, we cope together.", "docId": "130605pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "How is the community generally coping with it all, do you think?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "Well, look, I think if what you're trying to do is avoid the kind of terrorism that occurred in Boston or the kind of terrorism that almost occurred in Times Square a couple years ago, I'm for whatever it takes as long as it's restricted to the National Security Agency and doesn't get involved in looking for criminal behavior or other kind of things.", "docId": "130605pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "What do you make of it?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "Let me go back to 2006.", "docId": "130605pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "So, isn't it like for like?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "Let me say, first of all, I don't believe Colin Powell lied.", "docId": "130605pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "Why would you trust them anymore than you would trust the Obama administration with the same records?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "The president of the United States has decided that he wants as his national security adviser a person who went on five shows in one Sunday morning and miss -- you go back to lies.", "docId": "130605pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "What is your reaction to this news?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "No --", "docId": "130605pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "In a wonderful display of bipartisanship, would you have had exactly the same view?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "Piers, the difference is you're totally confusing the situations.", "docId": "130605pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "What is the difference?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "Well, the first -- I said part of the difference is, there is no question that the Obama administration and Secretary Clinton's staff systematically lied to the American people knowingly.", "docId": "130605pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "What is the difference?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "That's why I said.", "docId": "130605pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "But there is no evidence she did, though, is there?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "I find that a disappointing appointment on the part of the president.", "docId": "130605pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "Do you have any reaction to that?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "Well, this is going to be a bad show because I agree with you.", "docId": "130605pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "What is your view?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "I actually didn't watch it closely enough to have a clue.", "docId": "130605pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "Did she do a good job or not a good job?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130605pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "Are these the kind of things from your experience that can trigger in a young teenage girl like Paris with the background of her father's death and so on this kind of dramatic cry for help, if that's what it is?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "Yes, absolutely.", "docId": "130605pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "Shaun, I mean, how much do you think goes back to the fact that she lost her father who she was incredibly close to?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "We did not know it was a world record.", "docId": "130605pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "Do you know yet if it's a world record?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "It's a pending world record right now.", "docId": "130605pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "Yes, what I meant was, do you know yet, now that you have had it examined and weighed and stuff, do you know if you've broken the report?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "Yes, it -- it is terrifying, but any time you're that close to an apex predator or a food source, you really feel like you're just floating out there, and it's a very big shark teeth, they move around like lightning.", "docId": "130605pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "But wasn't it terrifying?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "130605pmt", "aSentId": 596, "question": "What is the technique for actually getting one of these things out of the water and on to a boat and taking it home with you?", "qSentId": 595}]